

# **ASIM SHAKOOR**

WEB DEVELOPER

### **CONTACT INFO**



+92 301 9804481



fa20bse020asim@outlook.com



https://asimshakoor11.github.io/ asim portfolio.com/



Jhelum, Punjab, Pakistan

### **EDUCATION**

2020 - 2024

BSC Software Engineering **MUST University** 

**FSC Pre-Engineering** APS, Jhelum Cantt

Matric

APS, Rawalpindi

## **LANGUAGES**

English	80%
Urdu	100%

## **PROFILE**

Hi. I'm Muhammad Asim Shakoor and I'm a front end web developer. I'm currently studying in 5th Semester of BSC Software Engineering at Must University, Mirpur Ajk. I'm front end developer of websites, and learning the expertise of websites as well.

I also have knowledge of working in adobe ilustrator and adobe photoshop. I will create for you any type of front end webpages or a complete a font end websites. My details and expertise are mentioned as well. Thanks!

# **EXPERIENCE**

2020-2022 **SELF WORKING** 

#### FRONT END WEBSITES

I have an experience of more than 2 year in developing front end of websites or webpages. I'm available for front end web development

2020 - 2022 **SELF WORKING** 

#### PROGRAMMING LANGAUGES

I have experience of working in different programming language. such as C#, C++ ,Java, Object oriented programing, HTML5, CSS3, Javascript. I can done any type of programming coding for you in these langauages.

2018 - 2022 **SELF WORKING** 

### ADOBE PHOTSHOP & ILLUSTRATOR

I have experience of designing and creating different logos and designs in Adobe Illustrator. I also have experience of converting PSD format to website including HTML, CSS, javascript

## PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

